What are you drawing over there?
Tu dessines quoi ?
A hypothetical containment field for a Frisbee-sized wormhole...
Un confinement pour un trou de ver de la taille d'un frisbee
...that could serve as a portal to a parallel universe.
qui peut servir de portail vers un univers parallèle.
Oh, you silly doodlebug.
C'est trop mignon.
A lot of scientists believe making contact with other life-forms...
Les scientifiques pensent que contacter d'autres formes de vie
...would probably not end well for us.
pourrait mal ﬁnir pour nous.
It's a Frisbee-sized wormhole, Leonard.
Il a la taille d'un frisbee, Leonard.
You could block it with a Frisbee. Calm down.
Tu peux le bloquer avec un frisbee. Détends-toi.
Do you expect me to build this? Heh.
Tu veux que je construise ça ?
I expect you to wipe the pudding off your chin. Gentlemen.
Je veux que tu essuies la purée surton menton. Messieurs.
Have you guys ever noticed that Sheldon always disappears every day at 2:45?
Vous avez vu que Sheldon disparait tous les jours a 14h45 ?
-Really? -He probably just goes to the bathroom.
- C‘est vrai ? - Il vajuste aux toilettes.
Actually, no. He goes at 8 am. with optional follow-ups...
Non, il y va a 8 h, avec parfois des compléments
...at 1:45 and 7:10 on high-fiber Fridays.
a13h45 et 19h10, les vendredis riches en fibres.
It's sad that you know that.
C‘est triste que tu saches ça.
I'm looking at his public calendar.
Je regarde son agenda.
Two-forty-five to 3:05, nothing.
De 14h45 a15h05, rien.
Yesterday, 2:45 to 3:05, nothing.
Hier, de 14h45 a15h05, rien.
Last week, nothing. Last month, nothing.
La semaine dernière, rien. Le mois dernier, rien.
He never has anything booked during that time.
Il ne prévoitjamais rien dans ce créneau horaire.
Twenty minutes a day completely unaccounted for.
20 minutes parjour, totalement inexpliquées.
-We should figure out where he goes. -Ooh, this is exciting.
- Il faut trouver où il va. - C‘est excitant.
Like one of my classic murder-mystery dinner parties.
Comme dans mes soirées de meurtre et mystère.
Right, the case of who murdered three Saturday nights of my life.
Quand on a assassiné trois samedis soirs de ma vie.
Colonel Koothrappali in the kitchen with the olive spread.
Le colonel Koothrappali dans la cuisine avec les olives.
It was tapenade and you guys suck.
C‘était de la tapenade et vous êtes nuls.
So how was work today?
Ça a été au travail ?
Well, I spent most of the afternoon growing isotopically pure crystals...
J'ai passé l'après-midi à créer des isotopes de cristaux
...for neutrino detection.
pour la détection de neutrinos.
That sounds like fun.
Ça a l‘air sympa.
-Yeah, it was. -Oh, good, I guessed right.
- Ça l'est. - Super, je suis tombée juste.
-Who you talking to? -Oh, just this guy I met at school.
- Tu parles a qui ? - A un type de mon école.
Oh, great. We're still dating, right?
Super. On sort encore ensemble ?
Relax, he's just a friend. We're doing an oral report together. He's really nice.
C‘est un ami. On fait un exposé oral ensemble.
I'm sorry, what was that? I had a little stroke after "oral."
Pardon, tu as dit quoi ? J'ai décroché après ”oral".
Would you stop?
Tu veux bien arrêter ?
He moved here from London. He doesn't know anybody.
Il arrive de Londres. Il ne connait personne.
Oh, good, an English accent, the sexiest accent you can have.
Génial, un accent anglais, le plus sexy des accents.
No, that's not true.
Ce n‘est pas vrai.
There's French, there's Italian.
Il y a l'accent français, l'accent italien.
No, you're right, it's the best.
Non, tu as raison. C‘est le mieux.
-Did you tell him you have a boyfriend? -It didn't come up.
- Tu as dit que tu as un copain ? - Ça ne s‘est pas présenté.
Maybe you should tell him.
Tu devrais peut-être lui dire ?
What am I supposed to say?
Tu veux que je lui dise quoi ?
Say, "Can't talk right now. Hanging with my boyfriend.
”Je ne peux pas te parler. Je suis avec mon copain.
England sucks, you suck, U.S.A. number one."
Tu es nui, l‘Angleterre est nulle, vive les États—Unis."
Fine. "Hanging with my boyfriend. Talk to you later."
”Je suis avec mon copain. A plus tard."
-Happy? -Yes. Thank you.
- Tu es content ? - Oui. Merci.
-What did he say? -Nothing.
- Il adit quoi ? - Rien.
What?
Quoi ?
"Did your boyfriend make you type that?"
“C‘est ton copain qui t‘a demandé d'écrire ça ?"
I hate this guy.
Je déteste ce type.
-Don't be like that. -Oh, come on. Trust me, he's hitting on you.
- Arrête un peu. - Crois-moi, il te drague.
He's not, we're just friends. Is this gonna be a problem?
Non, on est seulement amis. Ça va être un probléme ?
He's supposed to come over tomorrow to work.
Il doit venir demain pour qu'on travaille.
Really? Here?
Vraiment ? Ici ?
If it makes you uncomfortable, I'll switch partners even though the thing's due...
Si ça te gêne, je peux changer, même si c‘est obligatoire
...and everyone already has a partner and I'll probably end up failing the class.
et que tout le monde a un partenaire et que je serai sûrement recalée.
That'd be great. Thank you.
Ce serait parfait. Merci.
Two forty-four. Right on schedule.
14h45. Pile à l'heure.
Hey, Sheldon.
Salut, Sheldon.
Oh, hello.
Salut.
Raj and l are heading over to the genetics lab to pet the glow-in-the-dark bunny.
On va au labo de génétique caresser le lapin phosphorescent.
-Wanna come with us? -No, thank you.
- Tu veux venir ? - Non, merci.
You sure? They turn off the lights and it's like a little laser show that poops all over.
Tu es sûr ? Dans le noir, c‘est un spectacle crotte et lumière.
I'm quite sure. Good day.
J'en suis sûr. Bonne journée.
-Where are you going?
- Tu vas où ? - Vous allez où ?
-We told you. -Yeah, ljust told you.
- On te l‘a dit. - Je vous l'ai dit.
-No, you didn't. -Your word against mine. See you in court.
- Non, tu n'as rien dit. - Votre parole contre la mienne.
-Should we follow him? -I don't know. I'm torn.
- On le suit ? - Je suis partagé.
I want to know where he's going but now I kind of want to play with the bunny.
Je veux savoir où il va, mais je veux jouer avec le lapin.
-Hey, guys. -Hey, Alex.
- Salut. - Salut, Alex.
-Do you know where your boss just went? -No.
- Tu sais où va ton patron ? - Non.
-Don't you know his schedule? -All I know is corduroy...
- Tu connais son programme ? - Je sais que le velours
...makes too much noise and l have to go find quieter pants.
est trop bruyant et que je dois changer de pantalon.
Come on.
Viens.
Boy, what I wouldn't give to get her out of those pants.
Je paierais cher pour lui ôter son pantalon.
And into something a little more stylish.
Et pour lui en remettre un plus distingué.
This is where he goes?
C‘est ici qu'il va ?
-What's in there? -I think it's an old storage room.
- C‘est quoi ? - Une ancienne salle de rangement.
What could he be doing in there every day for 20 minutes?
Que fait-il ici tous les jours pendant 20 minutes ?
Well, he's not doing 20-minute abs...
Il ne fait pas d'abdos,
...because if he were, he'd have way better abs.
car il aurait de meilleurs abdos.
-Can you hear anything? -Not yet.
- Tu entends quelque chose ? - Pas encore.
What are you doing?
Tu fais quoi ?
I'm listening.
J‘écoute.
Can't you face the other way and listen?
Tu peux regarder de l‘autre côté et écouter ?
I can't do anything right for you, can I?
Ce que je fais n‘estjamais assez bien pour toi.
What the hell is he up to?
Qu‘est—ce qu'il fabrique ?
He is kind of a weirdo.
C‘est un peu un illuminé.
Maybe he's got Leonard Nimoy chained up in there.
Il retient peut-être Leonard Nimoy prisonnier.
Or Bill Gates. Or Stephen Hawking.
Ou Bill Gates. Ou Stephen Hawking.
Why would he chain up Stephen Hawking?
Pourquoi il retiendrait Stephen Hawking prisonnier ?
Howard, you can't treat the man differently just because he's disabled. That's not okay.
Tu ne peux pas traiter un handicapé différemment. C‘est mai.
If you're wondering why I've been staring...
Si tu te demandes ce que je regarde,
...l'm trying to get a look at this guy who's coming over to Penny's.
j'essaie d'apercevoir le type qui Vient chez Penny.
To be honest, I didn't know you were here.
En toute franchise, j'ignorais que tu étais ici.
It's not a big deal. He's just in her history class.
Ce n‘est rien. Il est dans sa classe d‘histoire.
They're working on a project. I don't even know why I care.
Ils font un projet ensemble. Pourquoi je m'en fais ?
-You know what, I don't care. -You think you don't care.
- Ça m‘est égal. - C‘est ce que tu crois.
This is silly. I have nothing to worry about.
C‘est idiot. Je n'ai aucune raison de m'inquiéter.
Oh, I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
Hey, statistically speaking, I'm sure you have something to worry about.
Si on regarde les statistiques, tu as de quoi t'inquiéter.
What do you mean?
Comment ça ?
Well, if we assume that your looks are average...
Si on part du principe que ton physique est moyen,
...right off the bat, 50 percent of men on Earth are more attractive than you.
50 % des hommes sur Terre sont plus séduisants que toi.
That's 1.5 billion handsome lads standing by, waiting to rain on your parade.
Ça fait 1,5 milliard de beaux gosses qui attendent de gâcher ta fête.
Well, yeah, but this isn'tjust about looks.
Il n‘y a pas que le physique qui compte.
I'm way above average in a lot of other things.
Je suis au-dessus dela moyenne dans d'autres domaines.
Not height, vision, athleticism, or ability to digest dairy products.
Pas la taille, la vue, les muscles, la digestion des produits laitiers.
I'm talking about important things like emotional maturity.
Je parle de choses importantes, comme la maturité émotionnelle.
You were just spying on your girlfriend through a peephole.
Tu espionnes ta petite copine a travers un judas.
I liked it better when you thought I wasn't here.
Je préférais quand tu pensais que je n‘étais pas la.
I'm not saying you don't have attractive qualities.
Mais tu as aussi des qualités attirantes.
Your choice of friends is impeccable.
Tu sais choisir tes amis àla perfection.
You're a good sleeper.
Tu dors bien.
And last but not least, you buy the grapes I like.
Et pour couronner le tout, tu achètes le raisin que j‘aime.
You're a real catch compared to some snoring guy...
Tu es bien plus attirant qu'un ronfleur
...with a fridge full of lousy grapes.
avec un frigo plein de raisins insipides.
None of this matters.
Ça n‘a pas d‘importance.
I trust that Penny cares about me and nothing's gonna happen with this guy.
Je sais que Penny tient a moi et qu'il ne se passera rien.
Unless of course he's a skilled hypnotist.
Sauf si ce type est un bon hypnotiseur.
What?
Quoi ?
While unlikely, it's still a statistical possibility.
C‘est peu probable, mais c‘est une possibilité.
She might be performing sexual acts with him and not even know it.
Elle peut s‘envoyer en l‘air avec lui sans s'en rendre compte.
-Now you're just being ridiculous. -Am I?
- Tu dis n‘importe quoi. - Tu crois ?
The mind's a mysterious thing, Leonard.
L'esprit est une chose mystérieuse, Leonard.
He could be having the time of his life...
Il peut prendre son pied pendant qu'elle croit
...while she thinks she's a chicken pecking for corn.
qu'elle est une poule picorant du mais.
Look at us, sneaking around in the middle of the night like a couple of cat burglars.
On se faufile au milieu dela nuit comme deux cambrioleurs.
I think we're more like ninjas.
On est plus comme des ninjas.
I don't wanna be a ninja. I wanna be a cat burglar.
Je ne veux pas être un ninja. Je veux être un cambrioleur.
-Fine. I'll be a ninja, you be a cat burglar. -No, we both have to be the same thing.
-Je suis un ninja, tu es un voleur. - Non, on doit être la même chose.
Okay, we're ninjas.
On est des ninjas.
Thank you.
Merci.
But next time we'll be cat burglars.
Mais la prochaine fois, on sera des cambrioleurs.
-lt's locked. -Are you sure?
- C‘est fermé. - Tu es sûr ?
Yes, I'm sure.
Oui, j'en suis sûr.
Now, you stand guard, I'm--
Monte la garde pendant que je…
It's locked.
C‘est fermé.
Just keep an eye out. I'll have this open in a minute.
Fais le guet. Je vais l'ouvrir en un rien de temps.
When did you learn how to pick locks?
Où as-tu appris a faire ça ?
When I was starting to do magic in junior high...
Quand j'ai commencé la magie au collège,
...I thought I could be an escape artist like Harry Houdini.
je pensais devenir le roi de l'évasion, comme Harry Houdini.
-How did that work out? -Pretty good.
- Tu as réussi ? - Pas trop mal.
I managed to escape friends, popularity, and every party thrown in a 12-mile radius.
Mes amis, ma popularité et toutes les fêtes m‘ont échappé.
-There. Ready? -Hold on, hold on.
- C‘est bon. Tu es prêt ? - Attends.
What?
Quoi ?
Sheldon is a very smart man, and he obviously wants to keep this a secret.
Sheldon est très intelligent et il veut garder son secret.
Yeah, so?
Et alors ?
What if it's booby-trapped?
Et si la pièce est piégée ?
Don't worry, I'm one step ahead of him.
Ne t'en fais pas, j‘y ai déjà pensé.
Oh, great, what's your pl--?
Super, c‘est quoi le plan ?
Are we good?
C‘est bon ?
Yeah.
Oui.
Forty-th ree.
Quarante-trois.
What the hell does that mean?
Qu‘est—ce que ça signifie ?
I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
-The solution to an equation? -Maybe.
- Le résultat d‘une équation ? - Peut—ètre.
It's a prime number.
C‘est un nombre premier.
Encryption systems are built on prime numbers.
Les systèmes d'encodage sont basés sur des nombres premiers.
What kind of secret does Sheldon have to encrypt?
Quel secret voudrait encoder Sheldon ?
He's always been very cagey about what he puts in his egg salad to make it so tasty.
Il a toujours caché ce qu'il mettait dans sa salade d'œufs.
It's paprika.
C‘est du paprika.
Really?
Ah bon ?
Well, okay, one mystery solved.
Bien, un mystère élucidé.
COLE: Okay, good night. PENNY: Thanks, Cole. See you at school.
- Bonne nuit. - Merci, Cole. A demain.
See you.
A demain.
I'll be right back.
Je reviens.
I thought you left a long time ago.
Je te croyais parti depuis longtemps.
What's up?
Ça roule ?
Hey.
Salut.
You, uh, moving into the apartment on the fifth floor?
Vous emménagez dans l‘appartement au cinquième ?
No. l was just visiting a friend.
Non, je venais voir une amie.
Oh, cool.
Super.
-That cute blond on 4? -Yeah. You know her?
- Lajolie blonde au quatrième ? - Vous la connaissez ?
Oh, well, I see her around.
Oui, on se croise.
I like to keep my distance because her boyfriend's a pretty scary dude.
Mais je garde mes distances, son copain est vraiment effrayant.
-Really? -Yeah.
- Vraiment ? - Oui.
He's ganged up.
Il fait partie d'un gang.
She told me he's a scientist.
Elle m‘a dit qu'il était scientifique.
That's the name of his gang.
C‘est le nom de son gang.
The Scientists.
Les Scientifiques.
They are crazy.
Ce sont des tarés.
-Well, thanks for the tip. -No problem, brother. Stay frosty.
- Merci pour le tuyau. - Pas de problème. Ouvrez l'œil.
We're still dating, right?
On sort toujours ensemble ?
-Oh, hello, Dr. Hofstadter. -Oh, hey, Alex.
- Bonjour, Dr Hofstadter. - Bonjour, Alex.
And call me Leonard. Dr. Hofstadter is my father.
Appelle—moi Leonard. Le Dr Hofstadter est mon pére.
And my mother.
Et ma mère.
And my sister.
Et ma sœur.
And our cat.
Et notre chat.
Although, I'm pretty sure Dr. Boots Hofstadter's degree was honorary.
Même si le diplôme du Dr Miaou Hofstadter n‘était qu'honorifique.
-May I join you, Leonard? -Sure.
- Je peux m‘asseoir ? - Bien sûr.
Thanks.
Merci.
Hey, Alex, let me ask you something.
J'ai une question, Alex.
My girlfriend knows this guy at school. He's got an English accent--
Ma copine a rencontré un type en cours. Il a un accent anglais...
Ooh, I love English accents.
J‘adore l'accent anglais.
Yeah, you all do.
Comme toutes les femmes.
Anyway, I feel like he's hitting on her.
J'ai l'impression qu'il la drague.
She says he's just being nice and I should trust her.
Elle me dit que je devrais lui faire confiance.
It's probably harmless.
C‘est sûrement innocent.
You know how it is. I'm sure you get hit on all the time.
Tu sais ce que c'est. Tu te fais sûrement souvent draguer.
Right.
Bien sûr.
Because girls are always like, "Ooh, that guy owns two Star Trek uniforms...
Les filles se disent: “Il a deux uniformes de Star Trek
...and gets a lot of ear infections. I gotta get me some of that."
et fait des otites chroniques. Il me le faut."
I don't know. Bet it happens more than you realize.
Ça arrive sûrement plus souvent que tu ne le crois.
Trust me, it doesn't.
Pas du tout.
You sure?
Tu en es sûr ?
You're cute, you're funny.
Tu es mignon, tu es drôle.
Maybe you're getting hit on and you don't even know it.
Tu te fais peut-être draguer sans t'en rendre compte.
Really?
Tu crois ?
I'm pretty sure.
J'en suis certaine.
Okay, I gotta get back to work. Thanks for listening.
Je dois retourner travailler. Merci de m‘avoir écouté.
-No problem. -Hope no girls rip my clothes off on the way.
- De rien. - Pourvu qu'aucune fille m'agresse.
Come on, we're smart guys.
On est intelligents.
-We can figure this out. -Forty-three.
- On peut trouver. - 43.
What is 43?
Qu'est-ce qui fait 43.
Besides my mom's neck size.
A part le tour de cou de ma mère.
It's the atomic number for technetium.
C‘est le numéro atomique du technétium.
That stuff's radioactive.
C‘est radioactif.
Do you think he's building a bomb?
Tu crois qu'il fabrique une bombe ?
It took him two years to put together that Lego Death Star. I'm not worried.
Non, il a mis deux ans a monter l'Etoile noire de Lego.
Ooh, this could be something.
J'ai une idée.
Forty-three is the number of calories in half a cup of fat-free yogurt.
43 est le nombre de calories dela moitié d'un yaourt allégé.
Why would you know that?
Comment tu sais ça ?
I'm sorry, we can't all eat whatever we want and still stay thin.
On ne peut pas tous manger ce qu'on veut et rester minces.
Wait. In The Hitchhikers Guide to the Galaxy...
Dans Le Guide du voyageur galactique,
...isn't 43 the answer to the question of life, the universe, and everything?
le 43 est la réponse àla question dela vie,
That's 42, dumb-ass.
C‘est le 42, triple buse.
Hey, hey.
Doucement.
Feelings.
Je suis sensible.
We should stop. I'm exhausted.
On devrait arrêter. Je suis épuisé.
Yeah, me too. We've got more important things to do.
Moi aussi. On a des choses plus importantes à faire.
Who cares what stupid 43 means?
Qui s‘intéresse à ce 43 débile ?
-Not me. -Let's go home.
- Pas moi. - On rentre chez nous.
-Want to get something to eat? -Sounds good.
- Tu veux aller manger ? - Bonne idée.
-What the balls is 43? -l have to know.
- C‘est quoi ce foutu 43 ? - Je dois savoir.
Hi.
Salut.
Hey. Shouldn't you be out with your gang...
Tu ne devrais pas être avec ton gang
...spray-painting equations on the side of buildings?
a tagger des équations sur des bâtiments ?
-Come on, I'm sorry. -I just can't believe you don't trust me.
- Je m‘excuse. - Tu ne me fais pas confiance.
No, I do. Of course I do.
Bien sûr que si.
Then why did you embarrass me in front of my friend? Who knew exactly who you were.
Tu m'as fait honte devant mon ami. Il savait qui tu étais.
-Really? -Your picture's on my refrigerator.
- C‘est vrai ? - Ta photo est sur mon frigo.
You know, I'm really starting to not like this guy.
Je commence vraiment a le détester.
What is your problem?
Tu épuises ton cerveau au travail et il ne t'en reste plus le soir ?
I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
It's hard sometimes.
C‘est difficile parfois.
Everywhere you go, guys hit on you.
Partout où tu vas, tu te fais draguer.
Even if I'm standing right there.
Même si je suis juste a côté.
And they're all taller than me. Why is everyone taller than me?
Ils sont tous plus grands que moi. Pourquoi ils sont tous grands ?
You know what, this is all in my head.
C‘est dans ma tête.
It's my problem, not yours.
Le problème Vient de moi.
Leonard, why do you always do this?
Pourquoi tu fais toujours ça ?
Listen to me. You are the one I'm with. You knowl love you.
Je suis avec toi. Tu sais que je t‘aime.
So will you please relax because you're driving me crazy.
Alors calme—toi parce que tu me rends dingue.
You know, that's the first time you ever said that you love me.
C‘est la première fois que tu me dis que tu m'aimes.
Yeah.
Oui.
We're just supposed to pretend it's not a big deal?
On fait comme si de rien n‘était ?
That's exactly what we're gonna do...
C‘est exactement ce qu'on va faire,
...because you're about to make me cry.
car tu es sur le point de me faire pleurer.
And we both know ifl start crying you're gonna start crying.
On sait que si je me mets à pleurer, tu vas pleurer aussi.
-You're right, you should go. -All right.
- C‘est vrai, vas-y. - D‘accord.
"Hey, it's Alex. Nice having coffee with you.
"C'est Alex. Sympa le café avec toi.
If you want to talk more, I'm always available." Smiley face, smiley face.
Si tu veux parler, tu peux compter sur moi." Smiley, smiley.
What a friendly girl.
Quelle chouette fille.
Okay, picture's up. Looks like the camera's working.
J'ai l'image. La caméra fonctionne.
That's good-quality video.
L‘image est de bonne qualité.
It better be. It's the spare camera for the Mars Rover.
J'espère bien. C‘est une caméra du Mars Rover.
How did you get your hands on that?
Où tu as trouvé ça ?
Million-dollar camera. Ten-dollar lock.
Une caméra à un million. Une serrure à 10 dollars.
Oh, my God, here he comes. This is it.
Mon Dieu, il entre. Ça y est.
-What the hell is that thing? -I don't know.
- C‘est quoi ce truc ? - Je ne sais pas.
SHELDON: This is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Ici le Dr Sheldon Cooper.
Experimental log.
Journal d'expérimentaﬁon.
Wormhole generator, test 44.
Générateur de trou de ver, les! 44.
Wormhole-generator test?
Un générateur de trou de verre ?
The first 43 parallel universes I've checked proved to be empty.
Les 43 premiers univers parallèles étaient vides.
I see no reason to suspect universe number 44 will be any different.
Rien n‘indique que l‘univers 44 sera diffèrent.
-Oh, my God! -Holy crap!
- Mon Dieu ! - La vache !
It's eating his face!
Il lui dévore le visage !
I found your webcam and replaced the video feed.
J'ai trouvé votre caméra etj'ai changé les images.
You two should be ashamed of yourselves.
Vous devriez avoir honte.
-Sheldon, we're really sorry. -Yeah, really sorry.
- On s‘excuse, Sheldon. - Oui, on s‘excuse.
Sorry?
Vous vous excusez ?
You may not realize it, but I have difficulty navigating certain aspects of daily life.
Vous l'ignorez, maisj'ai du mal a gérer certains aspects de ma vie.
You know, understanding sarcasm. Feigning interest in others.
Comprendre les sarcasmes. Feindre de s'intéresser aux autres.
Not talking about trains as much as I want to.
Ne pas parler de trains même si j'en crève d'envie.
It's exhausting.
C‘est épuisant.
Which is why, for 20 minutes a day, I like to go down to that room...
Alors, 20 minutes parjour, j'aime descendre dans cette pièce,
...turn my mind off, and do whatl need to do to recharge.
me déconnecter et faire ce que je fais pour me recharger.
But what are you doing in there?
Mais tu fais quoi là:—dedans ?
And what does 43 mean?
Que signifie le 43 ?
You don't need to know, you don't deserve to know...
Vous n'avez pas a le savoir, vous ne méritez pas de savoir
...and you will never know.
et vous ne le saurez jamais.
Yeah, well, I know how to make your egg salad now.
Je sais comment préparer ta salade aux œufs.
One, two, three, four...
Un, deux, trois, quatre
...five, six, seven, eight-- Drat.
cinq, six, sept, huit… Mince.
I'm never gonna get to 43 again.
Je ne referai jamais 43.
One, two, three, four-- Rats.
Un, deux, trois, quatre... Mince.
[English - us - an]
[French]